<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Baseline Protocol an Oasis Open Project on Baseline</title>
    <link>https://www.baseline-protocol.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Baseline Protocol an Oasis Open Project on Baseline</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.baseline-protocol.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>EY, ConsenSys, and Microsoft Announce Formation of Baseline Protocol Initiative to Make Ethereum Mainnet Safe and Effective for Enterprises</title>
      <link>https://www.baseline-protocol.org/news/launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.baseline-protocol.org/news/launch/</guid>
      <description>Industry leaders donate code to public domain through non-profit standards body, OASIS, and join thirteen founding organizations to further develop Baseline Protocol.
New York, NY, March 4, 2020 — ​Today, ​EY, ​ConsenSys​, and ​Microsoft announced the formation of the Baseline Protocol, an open source initiative that combines advances in cryptography, messaging, and blockchain to deliver secure and private business processes at low cost via the public Ethereum Mainnet. The protocol will enable confidential and complex collaboration between enterprises without leaving any sensitive data on-chain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.baseline-protocol.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.baseline-protocol.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Project Governing Board &amp;amp; Technical Leadership Governance for the Baseline project is managed by the Ethereum OASIS Project Governing Board and its Technical Steering Committee. These two groups ensure that all stakeholders have a voice in decisions affecting the work and that the contributions of developers, corporate supporters, and technology consumers are all valued.
Project Governing Board (PGB) The Project Governing Board provides top-level guidance and strategic direction for Baseline. The Board includes representatives from Ethereum OASIS Open Project Sponsors that have committed to the Entity Contributor Licensing Agreement.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>